Guide to the Doris Ulmann Photograph Collection ca. 1910-1934 PR 72
New-York Historical Society
- platinum blonde, long satin jacket over gown, holding an urn [St. Denis, Ruth, dancer, 1877-1968], 158562 (Item 656)
  founder Denishawn school of Dance, Los Angeles
- young woman, very long ringlets, embroidered blouse and smock with butterfly, 158561 (Item 657)
  #657 & 668 same woman
- hair pulled back, young, seated with book, 1917; 158560 (Item 658)
- 50's, seated, white collar, with pencil and musical score (?), 1916; 158559 (Item 659)
- from side, dark hair pulled back, low cut gown, 158558 (Item 660)
- white satin tie collar, with pencil, seated [Newman, Frances (see notes)], 158557 (Item 661)
- girl, hair pulled back, 158556 (Item 662)
- elderly, seated, elaborate lace collars, 158555 (Item 663)
  #618, 614, 663, 664 same woman
- elderly, seated, elaborate lace collars, 158554 (Item 664)
- dark, short, curled hair, pearl necklace, short sleeved dress, with shrubbery, 158553 (Item 665)
- seated at typewriter, 1918; 158552 (Item 666)
- seated, in turban, writing with pen at desk [Goudy, Bertha, type designer], 1918; 158551 (Item 667)
  #667, 946, 1381, 1395 same subject; per Margaret M. Clark July 1988 and notes in Xerox binder is Bertha Goudy
- young woman, very long ringlets, embroidered blouse and smock with butterfly, 158550 (Item 668)
  #657, 668 same woman
- very striking looking, late 20's-early 30's, dark hat or hair frames face, dark eyes, smart matching jacket and dress, gloves, 158549 (Item 669)
- seated, black dress, big brimmed hat with wide satin band, lace at collar and cuffs [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158548 (Item 670)
  same subject 670-672
- seated, black dress, big brimmed hat with wide satin band, lace at collar and cuffs [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158547 (Item 671)
- seated, black dress, big brimmed hat with wide satin band, lace at collar and cuffs [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158546 (Item 672)
  same subject, single portraits #670-672, 677, 679-683, 685, 686, 690; one of two women in #676, 678, 684, 687, 688-689
- portrait shoulders-up, lace collar, 158545 (Item 673)
  possibly same subject, single portraits #670-672, 677, 679-683, 685, 686, 690; one of two women in #676, 678, 684, 687, 688-689
- cropped page boy with bangs haircut, white blouse, sweater [Parrish, Anne], 158544 (Item 674)
  #674, 675, 2890 same subject, Anne Parrish (Bookman, Oct. 1930); image appears in Bookman December 1929
- cropped page boy with bangs haircut, white dress [Parrish, Anne], 158543 (Item 675)
- two women, one seated, one standing, with book [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158542 (Item 676)
  same subjects #676, 678, 684, 687, 688-689; one of subjects is also subject of single portraits #670-672, 677, 679-683, 685, 686, 690; one of two women in #676, 678, 684, 687, 688-689
- seated, black dress, lace cuffs [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158541 (Item 677)
- two women, one seated, one standing, with book [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158540 (Item 678)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar, black dress [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158539 (Item 679)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar, black dress [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158538 (Item 680)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar, black dress [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158537 (Item 681)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar, black dress [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158536 (Item 682)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar, black dress [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158535 (Item 683)
- two women, one seated, with books [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158534 (Item 684)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158533 (Item 685)
- seated, lace cuffs, collar [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158532 (Item 686)
- two women, both seated with books, one writing [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158531 (Item 687)
- two women, both seated with books [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158530 (Item 688)
- two women, both seated with books [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet & mother, Mary Warner Moore], 158529 (Item 689)
- standing with white bear's head [Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972, poet], 158528 (Item 690)
- white hair, short, beaded dress with shawl, with open book, 158527 (Item 691)
- white hair, lace collar, 158526 (Item 692)
- mother (or school teacher), two small girls, two small boys, with toys, 158525 (Item 693)
- group of five women, four in uniforms with white collars and ties, working on quilt (?), 158524 (Item 694)
- three boys, 158523 (Item 695)
  same subjects 695, 700
- two boys, man with white bear and straw hat, 158522 (Item 696)
- family on porch in front on cabin, father, mother, boy, baby, 1918; 158521 (Item 697)
- two boys and man seated at water pump with buckets, 158520 (Item 698)
  note on back in Ulmann handwriting: 68 Chores are over
- young pregnant woman with baby, two young girls, with buckets, 158519 (Item 699)
- three boys, 158518 (Item 700)
- two African American girls, one boy, with baskets, 158517 (Item 701)
- three boys, 158516 (Item 702)
- boy and girl at small bench or table, cups, saucers, 158515 (Item 703)
  same subjects #703, 708, 712
- boy, girl seated by fence post with school books, 158514 (Item 704)
  same subjects # 704, 710
- girl, boy, seated by steps or porch, 158513 (Item 705)
- boy in suit, vest, boy tie standing next to seated woman with book, 158512 (Item 706)
  same subjects #706-707
- boy in suit, vest, boy tie standing next to seated woman with book, 158511 (Item 707)
- boy and girl at small bench or table, cups, saucers, 158510 (Item 708)
- woman seated with small girl shelling peas or beans, 158509 (Item 709)
- boy, girl seated by fence post with school books, 158508 (Item 710)
  same subjects 704, 710
- two girls, in school clothes, 158507 (Item 711)
  same subjects #711, 713
- boy and girl at small bench or table, cups, saucers, 158506 (Item 712)
- two girls, in school clothes, 158505 (Item 713)
- two boys with gourds, pumpkins, 158504 (Item 714)
- white lab coat in front of black board [Palmer, Walter W., Associate Professor of Medicine, Columbia], 1918; 158503 (Item 715)
  #715, 1377, 1416, 1983, 2761 same subject, another image of subject in "XXIVV Portraits:.. ."
- glasses, tie, jacket, 158502 (Item 716)
  716-718 same subject
- glasses, tie, jacket, 158501 (Item 717)
- glasses, tie, jacket, 158500 (Item 718)
- glasses, tie, white lab coat, 1919; 158499 (Item 719)
- with microscope, 1918; 158498 (Item 720)
- white lab coat, 158497 (Item 721)
- white lab coat, 158496 (Item 722)
- bald, in surgical gown, with glasses, 1919; 158495 (Item 723)
- dark hair, mustache, with book [Burton-Opitz, Russell, Associate Professor of Physiology], 1918; 158494 (Item 724)
  subject is in "XXIV Portraits.. .", but not this image
- glasses, mustache, goatee [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158493 (Item 725)
  # 725, 728-732, 807, 1376, 1977, 1978 are same subject; different image of subject in "XXIV Portraits:.. ."
- with glasses, holding medical instrument [Gies, William J., Professor Biological Chemistry], 1918; 158492 (Item 726)
  #726, 2556, 2557, 2571, 2572 same subject; subject is in "XXIV Portraits.. ." but not this image
- fez, woven robe [Bata Kindai Amgoza Lo Bagolo], 158491 (Item 727)
  #455, 727, 1391,1401-1408, 1410, 2952 same subject; subject's name in handwriting (not DU) on back of mats 1401-1408, 1410
- mustache, goatee [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158490 (Item 728)
- mustache, goatee [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158489 (Item 729)
- mustache, goatee, in surgical gown and cap at operating table with patient, instruments [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158488 (Item 730)
- mustache, goatee [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158487 (Item 731)
- mustache, goatee, in surgical gown and cap [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 1919; 158486 (Item 732)
- dark hair, suit, 1919; 158485 (Item 733)
  #715-730 appear to be from either the Johns Hopkins portrait book or the Columbia University Phys. & Surgeons portrait book
- dark hair, Asian, with beakers, 1919; 158484 (Item 734)
  #734-735, 1378, 1379, 2905 same subject
- Asian, 1919; 158483 (Item 735)
- dark hair, mustache, 158482 (Item 736)
- two men, one seated in ornate chair, 1916; 158481 (Item 737)
  #715-730 appear to be from either the Johns Hopkins portrait book or the Columbia University Phys. & Surgeons portrait book, signature is unusual, printed in upper case letters
- woman in velvet gown, seated, with pewter or silver teapot, 158480 (Item 738)
- woman seated at table with book, bachelor's buttons in vase, 158479 (Item 739)
- woman seated, lame shawl, 158478 (Item 740)
- light colored hair, modern short haircut, holding face in hands, 158477 (Item 741)
- woman, hair in braids pinned up, silk shawl with vivid pattern, 158476 (Item 742)
- woman playing harp, 1917; 158475 (Item 743)
  same subject #743-748, 759
- woman playing harp, 1917; 158474 (Item 744)
- woman playing harp, 158473 (Item 745)
- woman playing harp, 158472 (Item 746)
  same subject #743-748, 759; is this Ulmann's sister? (tt)
- woman playing harp, 158471 (Item 747)
- woman playing harp, 1917; 158470 (Item 748)
- dark hair, seated, 158469 (Item 749)
- elderly, white hair pinned up, glasses, cameo, ribbon tie, 158468 (Item 750)
- brocade gown, short cropped dark hair [Gale, Zona], 158467 (Item 751)
  #751 & 931 same subject; per notes in Xerox binder and Margaret M. Clark, July 19, 1988, Zona Gale
- Asian, in kimono, head wrap [Fang, Mei Lang (? See notes)], 1919; 158466 (Item 752)
  # 752, 760-761, 880 same subject. Per Margaret M. Clark, Mei Lang Fang, male Chinese opera star; also possibly Michio Ito, female choreographer and performer
- on bed or bearskin rug, in silk pajamas (?), dark hair, 158465 (Item 753)
- dark hair, pearls, 158464 (Item 754)
- white hair, seated, crepe de chine blouse, velvet shawl [Chase, Edna Wooman, Editor, Vogue], 158463 (Item 755)
- white dress, dark scarf, dark curly short hair, 158462 (Item 756)
- dark hair, embroidered dress, 158461 (Item 757)
  same subject #757, 781, 783
- short curled light colored hair, dress with fur collar, 158460 (Item 758)
- woman playing harp, 158459 (Item 759)
- Asian [Fang, Mei Lang (? See notes)], 1919; 158458 (Item 760)
- Asian [Fang, Mei Lang (? See notes)], 1919; 158457 (Item 761)
- brocade gown, 158456 (Item 762)
- short, dark, curled hair, dark silk blouse, pearls, 158455 (Item 763)
- short curly hair, embroidered sleeves, unusual beaded necklace [Forbes, Esther], 158454 (Item 764)
- short dark hair, dress with ruffled trim, 158453 (Item 765)
  #765, 1790 same subject
- woman in shorts, dark hair, 158452 (Item 766)
- very short dark hair, dark dress, 158451 (Item 767)
- woman playing piano [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 1917; 158450 (Item 768)
  # 768, 770-772, 790, 870, 1765, 2951 same subject
- in front of cattails and decorative curtain, 158449 (Item 769)
- woman playing piano [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 1917; 158448 (Item 770)
- seated [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 1917; 158447 (Item 771)
- from side [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 1917; 158446 (Item 772)
- in diamond patterned jacket, in front of Boston Ivy, 158445 (Item 773)
  #773-775 same subject and identified in xerox book as Anne Parrish, but do not resemble Parrish, see 674-675t
- in diamond patterned jacket, in front of Boston Ivy, 158444 (Item 774)
- in diamond patterned jacket, in front of Boston Ivy, 158443 (Item 775)
- lace collar, pearls, 158442 (Item 776)
  same subject # 776-777
- lace collar, pearls, 158441 (Item 777)
- short dark hair, dress with short puffy sleeves, 158440 (Item 778)
  same subject # 778-780
- short dark hair, dress with short puffy sleeves, with cigarette, 158439 (Item 779)
- short dark hair, 158438 (Item 780)
- dark hair, embroidered dress, 158437 (Item 781)
- dark hair, long pearls, 158436 (Item 782)
  same subject #782, 784
- dark hair, embroidered dress, 158435 (Item 783)
- dark hair, long pearls, 158434 (Item 784)
- young woman, short sleeved sweater with embroidery on sleeve, with Emerson book, 158433 (Item 785)
- paisley gown, 158432 (Item 786)
- with book, ferns, 158431 (Item 787)
- dark wavy hair, dark blouse, 158430 (Item 788)
- dark hair, dark dress, 158429 (Item 789)
- waved dark hair, velvet gown, satin collar [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 158428 (Item 790)
- young, straight hair, very shiny, pulled back, floral print collar, 1919; 158427 (Item 791)
  #791-792 same subject
- long shiny hair pinned up, artist's smock, palette, brushes, still life painting, 158426 (Item 792)
- dark hair, embroidered or brocade trim on velvet gown with cat [Hurst, Fannie, American author (1889-1968)], 158425 (Item 793)
  #793, 1775 same subject
- gown with sheer jacket, locket, 1918; 158424 (Item 794)
- sleeveless gown, velvet, dark hair, 158423 (Item 795)
- young, short, cropped hair, freckles, 158422 (Item 796)
- with harp, white dress, 158421 (Item 797)
- in theatrical costume, velvet with brocade, 158420 (Item 798)
- pearls, embroidered sleeves on dress, short curly dark hair, 158419 (Item 799)
- velvet gown, short curly dark hair, lace trim at sleeves and collar [Widdeman, Margaret], 158418 (Item 800)
- velvet gown, short curly dark hair, lace trim at sleeves and collar [Widdeman, Margaret], 158417 (Item 801)
- velvet gown, short curly dark hair, lace trim at sleeves and collar [Widdeman, Margaret], 158416 (Item 802)
- beaded straps, pleated skirt [Widdeman, Margaret], 158415 (Item 803)
- velvet gown, lace trim at sleeves and collar [Widdeman, Margaret], 158414 (Item 804)
- velvet gown, lace trim at sleeves and collar [Widdeman, Margaret], 158413 (Item 805)
- velvet gown, beaded straps [Widdeman, Margaret], 158412 (Item 806)
- mustache, goatee [Hibbs, Russell A., Professor of Orthopedic Surgery], 158411 (Item 807)
- light colored hair, straight & longish, with long-necked stringed instrument, 1917; 158410 (Item 808)
  #808-809 same subject
- light colored hair, straight & longish, playing long-necked stringed instrument, 1917; 158409 (Item 809)
- holding papers [White, Clarence H.], 158408 (Item 810)
- suit, vest, tie, 158407 (Item 811)
- dark curly hair, bow tie, with cigarette, 158406 (Item 812)
  #812-813 same subject
- dark curly hair, with cigarette, 158405 (Item 813)
- velvet jacket, satin collar, white hair, 158404 (Item 814)
- mustache, 158403 (Item 815)
- bow tie, reading book [Whigham, H.J., Editor, Town and Country], 158402 (Item 816)
  #816, 1203, 1228, 3013 same subject; note on mat: H.G. Whigham, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image
- man, white hair and short beard, sideburns, at pulpit, 158401 (Item 817)
- girl with nurse's hat, white dress, sitting with doll in grass, 158400 (Item 818)
- girl with long ringlets climbing tree, 158399 (Item 819)
- girl in school uniform, (tie, white blouse), headband, writing at desk [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1918; 158398 (Item 820)
  #820, 822-823, 844-845, 849-852, 2645 same subject; compare to two images in Life and Photography of Doris Ulmann (Jacobs, 2001) pages 9, 11, 169
- girl in school uniform, (tie, white blouse), short ringlets, 158397 (Item 821)
- girl, white headband, embroidered blouse [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1917; 158396 (Item 822)
  #820, 822-823, 844-845, 849-852, 2645 same subject; identified compared to two images in Life and Photography of Doris Ulmann (Jacobs, 2001) pages 9, 11, 169
- girl, white headband, embroidered blouse [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1916; 158395 (Item 823)
  #820, 822-823, 844-845, 849-852 same subject; identified compared to two images in Life and Photography of Doris Ulmann (Jacobs, 2001) pages 9, 11, 169
- girl, short curly hair, embroidered blouse [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158394 (Item 824)
  #824, 833, 842, 846, 858-859, 987, 998, 1001-1003 same subject; per MM Clark is daughter of book editors Carl and Irita Van Doren
- girl, bare feet, short pants, white blouse, in doorway, 158393 (Item 825)
- girl sitting in grass, dark colored dress, short dark curly hair, striped socks, 158392 (Item 826)
  #826, 839 same subject
- girl, dark straight hair with bangs, white blouse with tie, dark cape, 158391 (Item 827)
- girl, straight short hair, bangs, white dress, 158390 (Item 828)
- blonde hair, 4-5 yrs. old, white dress, basket with grapes, 158389 (Item 829)
  #829-830 same subject
- blonde hair, 4-5 yrs. old, white dress, basket with grapes, in chair, bare feet, 158388 (Item 830)
- girl, light colored hair, cap, 158387 (Item 831)
- girl, dark long straight hair, flowered dress [Howard, Virginia, Brasstown, North Carolina, ca. 1933], 158386 (Item 832)
  identified from portrait of same subject, Featherstone book, p. 215
- short, dark curly hair, flowered dress [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158385 (Item 833)
- light colored, short cropped hair with bangs, plaid coat, with dog in doll carriage, 158384 (Item 834)
  #834, 837, 964 same subject
- girl at loom, 158383 (Item 835)
  #835-836 same subject
- girl at loom, 158382 (Item 836)
- light colored, short cropped hair with bangs, plaid coat, 158381 (Item 837)
  #834, 837 same subject
- girl, 3-5 yrs. old, white dress, blonde hair, short ringlets, 158380 (Item 838)
- girl, dark curly short hair, dark dress, 158379 (Item 839)
- girl, African American, white dress, standing by cabin, 158378 (Item 840)
  #840-841 same image
- girl, African American, white dress, standing by cabin, 158377 (Item 841)
- girl, dark curly hair, flowered dress [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158376 (Item 842)
- girl, light colored hair, ringlets with book, 158375 (Item 843)
  #843, 847, 854 same subject
- girl, white dress, sitting in play room with toys (teddy bears, dolls) [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1916; 158374 (Item 844)
- girl, school uniform, with doll [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 158373 (Item 845)
- girl, reading book, in garden or field [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158372 (Item 846)
- girl, light colored hair, ringlets, 158371 (Item 847)
- short, light colored straight hair, bangs, white dress, sitting at desk, 158370 (Item 848)
- girl, dark curly hair, fur cap, on scooter [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1916; 158369 (Item 849)
- dark hair, headband, embroidered blouse [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1916; 158368 (Item 850)
- girl, school uniform [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 1918; 158367 (Item 851)
- girl at piano [Necarsulmer, Evelyn, Ulmann's niece], 158366 (Item 852)
- girl, in rocking chair, dark hair, braid, 1917; 158365 (Item 853)
- girl, light colored hair, ringlets, 158364 (Item 854)
- girl, white dress, long light colored hair, 158363 (Item 855)
  #855-857 same subject
- girl, white dress, long light colored hair, 158362 (Item 856)
- girl, white dress, long light colored hair, 158361 (Item 857)
- girl, short curly hair, embroidered dress [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158360 (Item 858)
- girl, short curly hair, embroidered dress [Van Doren, Margaret (see note)], 158359 (Item 859)
- girl, short, blond curly hair with doll in her lap, 158358 (Item 860)
  #860, 862 same subject
- girl with flowers, long hair, 158357 (Item 861)
- girl, short, blond curly hair, 158356 (Item 862)
- dark hair, sequined jacket, black gown, 158355 (Item 863)
- short dark hair, ruffled dress, holding cigarette, 158354 (Item 864)
- with flowers [Keller, Helen], 158353 (Item 865)
- with book (Braille) [Keller, Helen], 158352 (Item 866)
- short curly light gray hair, 158351 (Item 867)
  #867, 910-916 same subject
- white beads, 158350 (Item 868)
- dark hair, dark dress [see below], 158349 (Item 869)
- dark hair, velvet gown [Lewisohn, Mrs. Sam (Margaret Seligman)], 158348 (Item 870)
  # 768, 770-772, 790, 870, 1765, 2951 same subject; back of photo, handwritten: Mrs. Sam Lewisohn
- hair pinned up or braided, dress or jacket with flowered collar, 158347 (Item 871)
- bonnet, white shawl, with book [Shaker Sister Adelaide of Mt. Lebanon, New York, ca. 1925-26], 158346 (Item 872)
  #872, 1780, 1785 same sub
- dancer, white fringed gown, dark hair [Graham, Martha], 158345 (Item 873)
  #873-878 same subject
- dancer in costume [Graham, Martha], 158344 (Item 874)
- dancer in white dress [Graham, Martha], 158343 (Item 875)
- dancer [Graham, Martha], 158342 (Item 876)
- dancer in white fringed gown [Graham, Martha], 158341 (Item 877)
- dancer in white fringed gown [Graham, Martha], 158340 (Item 878)
- dancer or actress in long flowing gown, with flowers, 158339 (Item 879)
- Asian man or woman with ceramic vase [Ito, Michio ? (see notes)], 1919; 158338 (Item 880)
- dark curly hair in modern looking knit top with stripes, short dress [Tamirisi (? See notes)], 158337 (Item 881)
  in Xerox binders is identified as Tamirisi, see Theatre Arts Monthly, vol 15, No. 1 Feb 31 p. 116
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158336 (Item 882)
  #882-897 same subject
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158335 (Item 883)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158334 (Item 884)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158333 (Item 885)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158332 (Item 886)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158331 (Item 887)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158330 (Item 888)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158329 (Item 889)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158328 (Item 890)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158327 (Item 891)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158326 (Item 892)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158325 (Item 893)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158324 (Item 894)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158323 (Item 895)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158322 (Item 896)
- long strand of pearls, dark dress, white lace collar [Glasgow, Ellen, novelist], 158321 (Item 897)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158320 (Item 898)
  #898-909 same subject
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158319 (Item 899)
- lacy gown, long blond hair pinned up [Gish, Lillian], 158318 (Item 900)
- lacy gown, long blond hair pinned up, embroidering [Gish, Lillian], 158317 (Item 901)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158316 (Item 902)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158315 (Item 903)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158314 (Item 904)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158313 (Item 905)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158312 (Item 906)
- lacy gown, long blond hair [Gish, Lillian], 158311 (Item 907)
- lacy gown, long blond hair pinned up [Gish, Lillian], 158310 (Item 908)
- lacy gown, long blond hair pinned up [Gish, Lillian], 158309 (Item 909)
- short curly light gray hair, 158308 (Item 910)
  #910-916 same subject
- short curly light gray hair, 158307 (Item 911)
- short curly light gray hair, 158306 (Item 912)
- short curly light gray hair, 158305 (Item 913)
- short curly light gray hair, 158304 (Item 914)
- short curly light gray hair, 158303 (Item 915)